https://www.proponent.com/privacy/

Type and press enter to search PRIVACY STATEMENT AND COOKIESWe at Proponent thank you for visiting our website to learn more about our products and services. We are committed to protecting your information and have designed a policy to safeguard your personal information. PRIVACY STATEMENTProponent collects, processes and stores limited amounts of personal data when you visit our website. We are committed to adhering to the legal requirements of data protection in our headquarters country, the United States, as well as complying with applicable global privacy regulations. INCLUSIONSThis Privacy Statement pertains to Kirkhill Aircraft Parts Co., and all of its entities including Proponent, Avio-Diepen, Proponent Warranty & Repair Administration, AAXICO Technical Services, Kapco Global, and D+C- Airparts Battery GmbH.We are committed to protecting your privacy and will handle your personal data in accordance with this Privacy Statement. PERSONAL DATA AND INFORMATIONPersonal information means any information relating to an identified or identifiable natural person (“data subject”) e.g. name, address, telephone number and email address. We may collect your personal information to provide services to, or obtain services from, you. Personal information which we may ask you to provide includes your contact information (such as your name, address, telephone number and email address) and identification details. Proponent does not collect, process, or store sensitive personal data. In a future event where personal data might be collected, we will ask for your explicit consent and inform you of the purpose for this processing. Sensitive data includes information such as race, religion, ethnicity, union membership, or sexual orientation. We may also ask you to supply information to us from time to time, including when you report a problem with our services and when we ask you to complete surveys, questionnaires and feedback forms that we use for quality monitoring and research purposes.We may also collect your personal information to comply with legislative and regulatory requirements. MANAGING YOUR INFORMATIONYou have the right of refusing to share your personal information with us. If you choose not to provide the personal information we request, or you do not wish to identify yourself to us, we may not be able to provide you with the services or information you require.We may collect personal information directly from you or indirectly. Information may be provided electronically including information provided: through your use of our website (e.g. cookies); during phone calls with our representatives; when we deliver and administer our services to you; and on forms or other correspondence, in writing or electronically, completed by you.If we collect personal information about you from third parties we will let you know and if required obtain your consent to such processing. If we receive personal information about you that we have not requested and which is not relevant to provide our services or to obtain services from you, we will destroy or pseudonymize the information, unless we are required by law to keep the information. Our website may contain links to third party websites. Our terms do not apply to these sites and we are not responsible for how those sites use or share information. Questions regarding how a third party handles your personal information should be referred directly to the third party. RECRUITINGAs part of our recruitment process, we will process your personal data, as set out in this privacy policy. In order to evaluate your application we will review and process the information that you have made available in applications, correspondence, resumes, etc. We recommend that you do not disclose sensitive personal data, such as information revealing racial or ethnic origin, religion, trade union membership, sexual orientation, or health in your application. We may disclose your information to hiring managers. We may disclose such information if legally required to do so at the request of a governmental entity or regulatory authority or if we believe in good faith that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to legal requirements or comply with legal processes; (b) prevent a crime or protect national security; or (c) protect the personal safety of users or the public.If the job position requires you to complete personality tests or similar you will be informed hereof when we have processed your application. The results of such tests will be treated confidentially but will be included in our evaluation of your application. We may also perform a complete background search, with your explicit permission, depending on the position for which you are applying. Such information will also be treated confidentially and only with your consent. The basis for our processing of your personal data is your request for our evaluation of your application prior to the potential execution of an employment contract as well as your consent for certain processing.As part of our evaluation of you and your application, we may wish to take references from your previous and/or current employers. We will only take up references if you have provided us with the contact information of the individuals we may contact for reference. If you are offered a position with Proponent, your application and additional personal data obtained during the recruitment process will become part of your personnel record. Any consent that you may have provided during the application and/or recruitment process may be withdrawn at any time by contacting us. DATA PROTECTIONProponent has taken actions within our control against accidental or intentional manipulation, loss, destruction and against access by unauthorized persons. Our security procedures are continually enhanced as new technology becomes available. RECTIFYING AND DELETING INFORMATIONYou have the right at any time to access and review your information for inaccuracies. You may also withdraw your consent to our processing of your personal information, however, Proponent reserves to deny requests where information is directly related to individuals transacting on behalf of a business entity. In the case that a correction or deletion is denied, we will notify you with the business reason for denying said request. If you believe that the information we hold about you is inaccurate, out of date, incomplete, irrelevant or misleading, you can request its correction. Please note that you may be charged for reasonable costs incurred by us in the processing of, and response to your access request, including photocopying, supplying written reports, administration and postage. CONTACTING USIf you have concerns or would like to contact our Data Processing division directly, you may send a written request to the following:Proponent, c/o Data Protection Division, 3120 Enterprise Street, Brea, California, 92821, U.S.A.We will endeavor to resolve your complaint as quickly as possible. POLICY UPDATESWe may review, amend or revise our Privacy Statement and the way we process personal information from time to time. We will post the updated Privacy Statement on our website. Any revised terms will take effect from the date of posting. COLLECTION AND STORAGE OF COOKIESCookies are very small text files that are stored on your computer when you visit certain websites. We use cookies to identify your device to improve and customer user experience, track purchasing contents, and identify where you are in the order process. This activity is required for our website to function properly. You can disable any cookies already stored on your computer but this might directly impact your ability to transact with us.In addition to the above, we store cookies to track the pages you visit using Google Analytics, allow you to share content on social media sites, and otherwise interact with our website content. We will not share or sell your personal information with third parties.ProductsInteriorEngineAirframeCockpitLiteratureServices & SolutionsFor CustomersServices & SolutionsWarranty and RepairAOG SupportFor Manufacturers and SuppliersServices & SolutionsManufacturingHose DivisionFly-Away KitsManufacturing CapabilitiesCustomer ResourcesGeneral InformationQuality Systems & ApprovalsValue Added Distributor (VAD) ApprovalsPMA Model EligibilitySupplier ResourcesGeneral InformationBarcode GeneratorSupplier Terms & ConditionsNew Company ApplicationLiteratureAbout UsCorporate CultureMeet Our TeamEmployee OwnershipCareersLiteratureEventsNewsContactProCartBarcode Generator
Open Welcome Popup Please note:We have closed our facility in Tamarac due to Tropical Storm Eta on 11/9/20 and will reopen on 11/10/20.
× Call Our AOG Hotline+ 1-205-650-4938 EXT. 3**To protect public and employee safety and health, Proponent is temporarily restricting 3rd party access to facilities during off-hours.  Our warehouses and customer service teams will be available to assist when Proponent opens the next business day.Shipping From:CaliforniaFloridaThe Netherlands LEARN MORE
×
Become a Supplier YOUR NAME*COMPANY*YOUR EMAIL* PHONEMESSAGE*PhoneThis field is for validation purposes and should be left unchanged.
×
We're Only As Good As the Information We HaveSharing your feedback and suggestions with us helps make Proponent a better aerospace distributor and a better partner to you. YOUR NAME*YOUR EMAIL* MESSAGE*CommentsThis field is for validation purposes and should be left unchanged.
× is nowAs of December 1, 2018, Avio-Diepen has been integrated with Proponent.
×
